

# **NGUYEN VAN A**

### **MARKETING MANAGER**

Male

**May 19, 1992** 

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and our power of choice is untrammelled and when nothing prevents our being able to do what we I of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

### **EDUCATION**



### **FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY**

major. to the claims o administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

#### FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

# **EXPERIENCE**



Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult ternative and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **Recognition and Gains:**

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

### **CVPRO JSC**

Sale Executive

### Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to since the 15 goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

# **ACTIVITIES**

Sep 2003 - 2007

### **CVPRO JSC**

#### Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer occasionally circumstances occur in which toil and pain can procure him some g' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

### **CERTIFICATIONS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 2004

## **HONORS & AWARDS**



**TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO** 

2013 - 2014

# **ADDITIONAL INFORMATION**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US ts to have it, simpl

### **REFERENCES**



### **NGUYEN VAN BINH**

director of cvpro jsc

mbinhnv@topcv.com **U** 01234567890

### **SKILLS**



Words Photoshop Excel English Power Point • Japanese

### **INTERESTS**



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt se quam nihi and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities